http://www.utahbridge.com/privacy-policy

HomePlay Bridge at HomeClubsContactEventsAll Upcoming EventsSummer SectionalFall SectionalSt. George SectionalWinter SectionalNewsLessonsNeighboring UnitsFAQs & LinksPrivacy PolicyMoreHomePlay Bridge at HomeClubsContactEventsAll Upcoming EventsSummer SectionalFall SectionalSt. George SectionalWinter SectionalNewsLessonsNeighboring UnitsFAQs & LinksPrivacy PolicyACBL Unit 386ACBL Unit 386ACBL Unit 386ACBL Unit 386ACBL Unit 386ACBL Unit 386ACBL Unit 386ACBL Unit 386HomePlay Bridge at HomeClubsContactEventsNewsLessonsNeighboring UnitsFAQs & LinksPrivacy Policy
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for Utahbridge.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. 1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about special events, new classes, etc.Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:· See what data we have about you, if any.· Change/correct any data we have about you.· Have us delete any data we have about you.· Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.At present, Utahbridge.com does not collect sensitive information (such as credit card data). Should this change in the future, that information will be encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 480-221-0685 or dein17@aol.com.Cookies
We do not use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help improve your access and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, cookies can be used to track and target the interests of our users. While we do not use cookies for internal purposes, it is possible that cookies are used when accessing this site from a third party (such acbl.org or google.com), or when clicking links that take you to external pages (such as acbl.org or hotel pages).Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Providing Personal Information
Should a blog or online partnership desk ever be added to this site, participation is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose any information requested. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and phone number), and Masterpoint holdings or convention agreements.
Copyright © 2019 Utah Bridge - All Rights Reserved.Powered by GoDaddy Website Builder
